{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"6.3/0.09",
			"answer":"6.3/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.8/0.006",
			"answer":"1.8/0.006",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"9.64/0.02",
			"answer":"9.64/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.672/4",
			"answer":"0.672/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"20/5",
			"answer":"20/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"480/8",
			"answer":"480/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.04/0.04",
			"answer":"8.04/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"71.1/0.9",
			"answer":"71.1/0.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.028/0.7",
			"answer":"0.028/0.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"67.6/0.2",
			"answer":"67.6/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.55/3",
			"answer":"2.55/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.864/0.8",
			"answer":"0.864/0.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"65.7/0.009",
			"answer":"65.7/0.009",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.22/0.09",
			"answer":"5.22/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.903/0.03",
			"answer":"0.903/0.03",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}